A Guide to the Blanchette H. Rockefeller Papers FA107
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Subject Files, 1933-1994; 53/3; 16 Cubic Feet 40 Boxes
  - Asia Society - Correspondence, 1959, 1961, (1978-1992) (Box 16, Folder 121)
  - Asia Society - Asia House Gallery, 1961-1979 (Box 16, Folder 122)
  - Asia Society - Asia House Gallery, 1961-1979 (Box 16, Folder 123)
  - Asia Society - Asia Society Galleries, 1981-1992 (Box 16, Folder 124)
  - Asia Society - Asia Society Galleries - Mr. and Mrs. John D. Rockefeller 3rd Collection, 1967-1987 (Box 17, Folder 125)
  - Asia Society - New Headquarters (Box 17, Folder 126)
    Groundbreaking and dedication, 1979-1981 Dedication, April 4, 1981 Installation, Mr. and Mrs. John D. Rockefeller 3rd Collection, 1981
  - Asia Society - New Headquarters - Special Events, 1967-1992 (Box 17, Folder 127)
  - Asia Society - New Headquarters - Special Events, 1967-1992 (Box 17, Folder 128)
  - Asian Cultural Council - Correspondence, 1979-1986 (Box 17, Folder 129)
  - Asian Cultural Council - Correspondence, 1979-1986 (Box 17, Folder 130)
  - Asian Cultural Council - Correspondence, 1987-1993 (Box 18, Folder 131)
  - Asian Cultural Council - Correspondence, 1987-1993 (Box 18, Folder 132)
  - Asian Cultural Council - Meeting Agendas and Minutes, 1983-1991 (Box 18, Folder 133)
  - Asian Cultural Council - Meeting Agendas and Minutes, 1983-1991 (Box 18, Folder 134)
  - Awards - Legion d'Honneur, October 1988 (Box 19, Folder 135)
  - Biography - Rsums, 1954-1993 (Box 19, Folder 136)
  - Biography - John D. Rockefeller 3rd - "The Rockefeller Century", 1978-1988 (Box 19, Folder 137)
  - Biography - John D. Rockefeller 3rd - "The Rockefeller Century", 1978-1988 (Box 19, Folder 137A)
  - Biography - John D. Rockefeller 3rd - "The Rockefeller Conscience", 1992 (Box 19, Folder 138)
  - Children's Art Carnival, 1972-1984 (Box 19, Folder 139)
  - Christmas Cards Received, 1970-1984 (Box 19, Folder 140)
  - Chronological Files (A), 1978-1992 (Box 19, Folder 141)
  - Chronological Files (A), 1978-1992 (Box 19, Folder 141A)
  - Chronological Files (B), 1978-1992 (Box 19, Folder 142)
  - Chronological Files (C), 1978-1992 (Box 20, Folder 143)
  - Chronological Files (D), 1978-1992 (Box 20, Folder 144)
  - Chronological Files (D), 1978-1992 (Box 20, Folder 144A)
  - Chronological Files (E), 1978-1992 (Box 20, Folder 145)
  - Chronological Files (F), 1978-1992 (Box 20, Folder 146)
  - Chronological Files (G), 1978-1992 (Box 20, Folder 147)
  - Chronological Files (H), 1978-1992 (Box 20, Folder 148)
  - Chronological Files (I-K), 1978-1992 (Box 20, Folder 149)
  - Chronological Files (I-K), 1978-1992 (Box 20, Folder 149A)
  - Chronological Files (L), 1978-1992 (Box 20, Folder 150)
  - Chronological Files (M), 1978-1992 (Box 21, Folder 151)
  - Chronological Files (Mc), 1978-1992 (Box 21, Folder 152)
  - Chronological Files (N-O), 1978-1992 (Box 21, Folder 153)
  - Chronological Files (P), 1978-1992 (Box 21, Folder 154)
  - Chronological Files (Q-R), 1978-1992 (Box 21, Folder 155)
  - Chronological Files (Q-R), 1978-1992 (Box 21, Folder 155A)
  - Chronological Files (Sa-Sh), 1978-1992 (Box 21, Folder 156)
  - Chronological Files (Si-Sz), 1978-1992 (Box 21, Folder 157)
  - Chronological Files (Si-Sz), 1978-1992 (Box 21, Folder 157A)
  - Chronological Files (T), 1978-1992 (Box 21, Folder 158)
  - Chronological Files (U-Z), 1978-1992 (Box 22, Folder 159)
  - Citizens Committee for New York City, 1975-1992 (Box 22, Folder 160)
  - Citizens Committee for New York City - Benefits, 1978-1987 (Box 22, Folder 161)
  - Clubs - Cosmopolitan Club, 1945-1992 (Box 22, Folder 162)
  - Clubs - Cosmopolitan Club, 1945-1992 (Box 22, Folder 163)
  - Clubs - The River Club, 1955-1992 (Box 22, Folder 164)
  - Clubs - Sleepy Hollow Country Club, 1958-1986 (Box 22, Folder 165)
  - Clubs - Sleepy Hollow Country Club, 1987-1993 (Box 23, Folder 166)
  - Colonial Williamsburg, 1951-1978 (Box 23, Folder 167)
  - Colonial Williamsburg, 1951-1978 (Box 23, Folder 168)
  - Colonial Williamsburg - Abby Aldrich Rockefeller Folk Art Center, 1986-1992 (Box 23, Folder 169)
  - Colonial Williamsburg - Abby Aldrich Rockefeller Folk Art Center, 1986-1992 (Box 23, Folder 169A)
  - Colonial Williamsburg - Bassett Hall, 1965-1992 (Box 23, Folder 170)
  - Colonial Williamsburg - Bassett Hall - Bequeathal, 1979-1992 (Box 23, Folder 171)
  - Colonial Williamsburg - Bassett Hall - Bequeathal, 1979-1992 (Box 23, Folder 172)
  - Columbia Presbyterian Medical Center - Edward S. Harkness Eye Institute, 1990-1992 (Box 23, Folder 173)
  - Columbia University, 1955, 1980-1992 (Box 23, Folder 174)
  - Commission for Cultural Affairs for New York City, 1974-1981 (Box 24, Folder 175)
  - Community Service Society of New York - Board of Trustees, 1945-1949 (Box 24, Folder 176)
  - Community Service Society of New York - Family Service, 1947-1950 (Box 24, Folder 177)
  - Community Service Society of New York - 100th Anniversary, 1946-1948 (Box 24, Folder 178)
  - Community Service Society of New York - 101st Year Fund, 1949 (Box 24, Folder 179)
  - Community Service Society of New York - Yorkville District Community, 1946-1947 (Box 24, Folder 180)
  - Contributions, 1933-1935, 1944-1949 (Box 24, Folder 181)
  - Contributions, 1933-1935, 1944-1949 (Box 24, Folder 182)
  - Contributions, 1933-1935, 1944-1949 (Box 24, Folder 183)
  - Contributions, 1933-1935, 1944-1949 (Box 24, Folder 184)
  - Contributions, 1933-1935, 1944-1949 (Box 24, Folder 185)
  - Contributions, 1933-1935, 1944-1949 (Box 24, Folder 186)
  - Contributions, 1933-1935, 1944-1949 (Box 24, Folder 187)
  - Contributions - Bluebooks, 1975-1984 (Box 24, Folder 188)
  - Contributions - Bluebooks, 1975-1984 (Box 24, Folder 189)
  - Contributions - Bluebooks, 1985-1992 (Box 25, Folder 190)
  - Contributions - Bluebooks, 1985-1992 (Box 25, Folder 191)
  - Contributions - Requests Declined, 1944-1949 (Box 25, Folder 192)
  - Contributions - Requests Declined, 1944-1949 (Box 25, Folder 193)
  - Contributions - Requests Declined, 1944-1949 (Box 25, Folder 194)
  - Cultural Assistance Center - Planning Commission, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 195)
  - Debut Scrapbook, 1927-1928 (Box 26, Folder 196)
  - Engagement - Appointment Book, 1932 (Box 26, Folder 197)
  - Engagement - Letters from Family, 1932 (Box 26, Folder 198)
  - Engagement - Letters from Friends, 1932 (Box 26, Folder 199)
  - Engagement - Letters from Friends, 1932 (Box 26, Folder 200)
  - Engagement - Letters to Mrs. Elon H. Hooker, 1932 (Box 26, Folder 201)
  - Girl Scout Committee - Pocantico Hills, 1939-1943 (Box 26, Folder 202)
  - Households - One Beekman Place, 1978-1986 (Box 26, Folder 203)
  - Households - One Beekman Place, 1987-1992 (Box 27, Folder 204)
  - Households - One Beekman Place - Apartment 9A/10A, 1972-1980 (Box 27, Folder 205)
  - Households - One Beekman Place - Apartment 12A, 1978-1992 (Box 27, Folder 206)
  - Households - One Beekman Place - Cleaning, 1948-1949 (Box 27, Folder 207)
  - Households - One Beekman Place - House Rules, 1981-1992 (Box 27, Folder 208)
  - Households - Fieldwood Farm - General, 1978-1991 (Box 27, Folder 209)
  - Households - Fieldwood Farm - General, 1978-1991 (Box 27, Folder 210)
  - Households - Fieldwood Farm - Animals, 1956-1985 (Box 27, Folder 211)
  - Households - Fieldwood Farm - Bandler House, 1979-1988 (Box 28, Folder 212)
  - Households - Fieldwood Farm - Buildings, Plans, Etc., 1980 (Box 28, Folder 213)
  - Households - Fieldwood Farm - Garden, 1964-1987 (Box 28, Folder 214)
  - Households - Fieldwood Farm - Horses and Barns, 1974-1984 (Box 28, Folder 215)
  - Households - Fieldwood Farm - Horses and Barns - American Horse Shows Association, Inc. (AHSA) Lawsuit, 1991-1992 (Box 28, Folder 216)
  - Households - Fieldwood Farm - Horses and Barns - Carol diGiuseppe, 1973-1990 (Box 28, Folder 217)
  - Households - Fieldwood Farm - House - Miscellany, 1940-1989 (Box 28, Folder 218)
  - Households - Fieldwood Farm - Management - Bill Garrison, 1981-1985 (Box 28, Folder 219)
  - Households - Fieldwood Farm - Management - David Black, 1985-1989 (Box 28, Folder 220)
  - Households - Fieldwood Farm - Management - Farm Budgets, 1979-1990 (Box 29, Folder 221)
  - Households - Fieldwood Farm - Pietraszko House, 1979-1980 (Box 29, Folder 222)
  - Households - Fieldwood Farm - Property - 897 Sleepy Hollow Road, 1989-1991 (Box 29, Folder 223)
  - Households - Fieldwood Farm - Sheep - Scrapie Research, 1987-1988 (Box 29, Folder 224)
  - Households - Fieldwood Farm - Sheep - Susanna Davy, 1981-1992 (Box 29, Folder 225)
  - Households - Fieldwood Farm - Spencer House Renovations, 1979-1980 (Box 29, Folder 226)
  - Households - Millstream Cottage, 1961-1994 (Box 29, Folder 227)
  - Households - Millstream Cottage, 1961-1994 (Box 29, Folder 227A)
  - Households - Millstream Cottage, 1961-1994 (Box 29, Folder 228)
  - Households - Millstream Cottage, 1961-1994 (Box 29, Folder 228A)
  - Households - Millstream Cottage - Caretaker - Don Witherspoon, 1969-1981, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 229)
  - Households - Millstream Cottage - Casino and Golf Club, 1965-1978 (Box 29, Folder 230)
  - Households - New York City Apartments - 860 United Nations Plaza, 1974, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 231)
  - Households - New York City Apartments - Garage Apartments (West 55th Street), 1977-1986 (Box 30, Folder 232)
  - Households - New York City Apartments - 411 East 53rd Street, 1986-1994 (Box 30, Folder 233)
  - Hospitality - Lists - Dinner Parties, 1973-1980 (Box 30, Folder 234)
  - Hospitality - Lists - Fundraising (Box 30, Folder 235)
  - Hospitality - Lists - Wedding Gifts Given, 1947-1987 (Box 30, Folder 236)
  - India, 1959, (1980-1985), 1991 (Box 30, Folder 237)
  - In Memoriam - John D. Rockefeller 3rd - Condolences - Letters, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 238)
  - In Memoriam - John D. Rockefeller 3rd - Condolences - Letters, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 238A)
  - In Memoriam - John D. Rockefeller 3rd - Condolences - Letters, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 239)
  - In Memoriam - John D. Rockefeller 3rd - Condolences - Asia Society Book, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 240)
  - In Memoriam - John D. Rockefeller 3rd - Condolences - Index Cards, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 240A)
  - In Memoriam - John D. Rockefeller 3rd - Condolences - Japan House Book, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 241)
  - In Memoriam - John D. Rockefeller 3rd - Memorial Services - Riverside Church, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 242)
  - In Memoriam - John D. Rockefeller 3rd - Memorial Services - Japan and Asia Societies, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 243)
  - In Memoriam - John D. Rockefeller 3rd - Press Clippings, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 244)
  - In Memoriam - John D. Rockefeller 3rd - Tributes, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 245)
  - In Memoriam - Blanchette Hooker Rockefeller - Condolence Letters (A-L), 1992 (Box 32, Folder 246)
  - In Memoriam - Blanchette Hooker Rockefeller - Condolence Letters (M-Z), 1992 (Box 32, Folder 247)
  - In Memoriam - Blanchette Hooker Rockefeller - Memorial Booklet - Family and Friends, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 248)
  - In Memoriam - Blanchette Hooker Rockefeller - Memorial Booklet - Museum of Modern Art (MoMA), 1992 (Box 32, Folder 249)
  - In Memoriam - Blanchette Hooker Rockefeller - Memorial Booklet - Staff, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 250)
  - In Memoriam - Blanchette Hooker Rockefeller - Memorial Booklet - Working Papers, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 251)
  - In Memoriam - Blanchette Hooker Rockefeller - Memorial Booklet - Working Papers, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 251A)
  - In Memoriam - Blanchette Hooker Rockefeller - Memorial Service - Attendance, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 252)
  - In Memoriam - Blanchette Hooker Rockefeller - Memorial Service - Video Production Documents, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 253)
  - In Memoriam - Blanchette Hooker Rockefeller - Memorial Service - Video Recording, 1992 December 4; 1 inch videotape; Sound, Color, 80 minutes (Reel AV 11561)
    Access copy available.
    Scope and Contents
    Videorecording of memorial service for Blanchette Ferry Hooker Rockefeller at Riverside Church in New York City.
  - In Memoriam - Blanchette Hooker Rockefeller - Memorial Service - Working Papers, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 254)
  - In Memoriam - Blanchette Hooker Rockefeller - Memorial Service - Working Papers, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 254A)
  - In Memoriam - Blanchette Hooker Rockefeller - Obituaries/Press Clippings, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 255)
  - Japan - Correspondence (A-W), 1959, 1978-1992 (Box 33, Folder 256)
  - Japan - Correspondence (A-W), 1959, 1978-1992 (Box 33, Folder 257)
  - Japan - Correspondence - Embassy and Consul-General, 1979-1989 (Box 33, Folder 258)
  - Japan - Correspondence - Imperial Family, 1971-1992 (Box 34, Folder 259)
  - Japan - Correspondence - Imperial Family - Greeting Cards, 1978-1991 (Box 34, Folder 260)
  - Japan - Correspondence - Matsumoto Family, 1952-1989 (Box 34, Folder 261)
  - Japan - Correspondence - Misao (Matsumoto) & Fumihiko Maki, 1955-1992 (Box 34, Folder 262)
  - Japan - Fujisankei Communications (Box 34, Folder 263)
  - Japan - International House, 1972-1992 (Box 34, Folder 264)
  - Japan - Japanese Chamber of Commerce and Industry of New York, Inc., 1985-1992 (Box 35, Folder 265)
  - Japan - Japan Foundation, 1972-1992 (Box 35, Folder 266)
  - Japan - Japan Society, 1959-1990 (Box 35, Folder 267)
  - Japan - Japan Society - Annual Dinners, 1971-1991 (Box 35, Folder 268)
  - Japan - Japan Society - Annual Dinners, 1971-1991 (Box 35, Folder 269)
  - Japan - Japan Society Gallery, 1971-1991 (Box 35, Folder 270)
  - Junior Fortnightly, 1979-1992 (Box 35, Folder 271)
  - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts, Inc., 1970-1990 (Box 36, Folder 272)
  - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts, Inc. - The Chamber Music Society, 1982-1992 (Box 36, Folder 273)
  - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts, Inc. - The Juilliard School, 1966-1992 (Box 36, Folder 274)
  - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts, Inc. - The Juilliard School, 1966-1992 (Box 36, Folder 275)
  - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts, Inc. - The Juilliard School, 1966-1992 (Box 36, Folder 276)
  - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts, Inc. - The Metropolitan Opera, 1980-1992 (Box 36, Folder 277)
  - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts, Inc. - The New York Philharmonic, 1981-1993 (Box 36, Folder 278)
  - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts, Inc. - Vivian Beaumont Theater, 1985-1991 (Box 36, Folder 279)
  - Museums (A-Z), 1975-1989 (Box 37, Folder 280)
  - Museums (A-Z), 1975-1989 (Box 37, Folder 281)
  - Museums - Museum of Fine Arts, Boston, 1968-1992 (Box 37, Folder 282)
  - Museums - Museum of Fine Arts, Boston, 1968-1992 (Box 37, Folder 283)
  - Museums - Fine Arts Museums of San Francisco, 1978-1992 (Box 37, Folder 284)
  - Museums - Fine Arts Museums of San Francisco, 1978-1992 (Box 37, Folder 285)
  - Museums - Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1968-1985 (Box 38, Folder 286)
  - Museums - Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts, 1972-1986 (Box 38, Folder 287)
  - Museums - Museum Presidents' Conference, 1977-1987 (Box 38, Folder 288)
  - Museums - Museum Presidents' Conference, 1977-1987 (Box 38, Folder 289)
  - National Endowment for the Arts, 1975-1986 (Box 38, Folder 290)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1974-1976 (Box 38, Folder 291)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1977-1983 (Box 39, Folder 292)
  - New York City - Civic Events and Institutions, 1976-1988 (Box 39, Folder 293)
  - New York State - Government Relations, 1975-1989 (Box 39, Folder 294)
  - New York State Council on the Arts, 1977-1989 (Box 39, Folder 295)
  - New York State Council on the Arts, 1977-1989 (Box 39, Folder 296)
  - New York University, 1980-1982 (Box 39, Folder 297)
  - Personal Correspondence (A), 1965-1990 (Box 40, Folder 298)
  - Personal Correspondence (B), 1951-1989 (Box 40, Folder 299)
  - Personal Correspondence - Bandler, Jean and Ned, 1974-1990 (Box 40, Folder 300)
  - Personal Correspondence (C), 1963-1989 (Box 40, Folder 301)
  - Personal Correspondence - Cobb, Eliza Parkinson, 1967-1988 (Box 40, Folder 302)
  - Personal Correspondence (D-E), 1958-1991 (Box 40, Folder 303)
  - Personal Correspondence (F-I), 1933, 1979-1988 (Box 40, Folder 304)
  - Personal Correspondence (J-K), 1948, 1979-1991 (Box 40, Folder 305)
  - Personal Correspondence (L), 1979-1991 (Box 40, Folder 306)
  - Personal Correspondence (M), 1934-1956, (1979-1989) (Box 40, Folder 307)
  - Personal Correspondence (N), 1946-1956, 1975-1985 (Box 40, Folder 308)
  - Personal Correspondence (R-S), 1956, 1979-1992 (Box 40, Folder 309)
  - Personal Correspondence - Roberts, Laurence and Isabel, 1971-1991 (Box 41, Folder 310)
  - Personal Correspondence - Sherfield, Lord and Lady (Makins, Roger & Alice), 1951-1986 (Box 41, Folder 311)
  - Personal Correspondence (T), 1979-1991 (Box 41, Folder 312)
  - Personal Correspondence (V-Z), 1951-1987 (Box 41, Folder 313)
  - Personal Correspondence - Acknowledgement Letters, 1973-1985 (Box 41, Folder 314)
  - Personal Correspondence - Birthdays, 1984, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 315)
  - Personal Correspondence - Declination Letters, 1991-1995 (Box 41, Folder 316)
  - Personal Correspondence - Declination Letters, 1991-1995 (Box 41, Folder 317)
  - Personal Correspondence - Recommendation Letters, 1946-1965, 1974-1984 (Box 41, Folder 318)
  - Personal Correspondence - Recommendation Letters, 1946-1965, 1974-1984 (Box 41, Folder 319)
  - Phelps Memorial Hospital Center, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 320)
  - Population Council, 1978-1992 (Box 42, Folder 321)
  - Princeton University, 1979-1989 (Box 42, Folder 322)
  - Princeton University, 1979-1989 (Box 42, Folder 322A)
  - Princeton University, 1979-1989 (Box 42, Folder 323)
  - Ramon Magsaysay Award Foundation, 1979-1989 (Box 42, Folder 324)
  - Riverside Church, 1933, 1980-1989 (Box 42, Folder 325)
  - Rockefeller Archive Center, 1979-1992 (Box 42, Folder 326)
  - Rockefeller Archive Center, 1979-1992 (Box 42, Folder 326A)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, 1978-1991 (Box 42, Folder 327)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, 1978-1991 (Box 42, Folder 327A)
  - Rockefeller Family Fund, 1983-1988 (Box 42, Folder 328)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1962-1991 (Box 42, Folder 329)
  - Rockefeller Public Service Awards, 1978-1979 (Box 42, Folder 330)
  - Rockefeller University, 1980-1988 (Box 42, Folder 331)
  - Rowntree Family - Rowntree, B. Seebohm, 1941-1954 (Box 43, Folder 332)
  - Rowntree Family - Rowntree, Peter (and Bessie) - Letters from, 1930 (Box 43, Folder 333)
  - Rowntree Family - Rowntree, Peter (and Bessie) - Letters from, 1940-1949 (Box 43, Folder 334)
  - Rowntree Family - Rowntree, Peter (and Bessie) - Letters from, 1940-1949 (Box 43, Folder 335)
  - Rowntree Family - Rowntree, Peter (and Bessie) - Letters from, 1940-1949 (Box 43, Folder 336)
  - Rowntree Family - Rowntree, Peter (and Bessie) - Letters from, 1940-1949 (Box 43, Folder 337)
  - Rowntree Family - Rowntree, Peter (and Bessie) - Letters from, 1940-1949 (Box 43, Folder 338)
  - Rowntree Family - Rowntree, Peter (and Bessie) - Letters from, 1940-1949 (Box 43, Folder 339)
  - Rowntree Family - Rowntree, Peter (and Bessie) - Letters from, 1940-1949 (Box 43, Folder 340)
  - Rowntree Family - Rowntree, Peter (and Bessie) - Letters from, 1940-1949 (Box 43, Folder 341)
  - Rowntree Family - Rowntree, Peter (and Bessie) - Letters from, 1940-1949 (Box 43, Folder 342)
  - Rowntree Family - Rowntree, Peter (and Bessie) - Letters from, 1940-1949 (Box 43, Folder 343)
  - Rowntree Family - Rowntree, Peter (and Bessie) - Letters from/to, 1950-1980 (Box 43, Folder 344)
  - Rowntree Family - Rowntree, Peter (and Bessie) - Envelope Samples, 1940-1944 (Box 43, Folder 345)
  - Rowntree Family - Rowntree, Peter (and Bessie) - Letters to, 1940-1949 (Box 44, Folder 346)
  - Rowntree Family - Rowntree, Peter (and Bessie) - Letters to, 1940-1949 (Box 44, Folder 347)
  - Rowntree Family - Rowntree, Peter (and Bessie) - Letters to, 1940-1949 (Box 44, Folder 348)
  - Rowntree Family - Rowntree, Peter (and Bessie) - Letters to, 1940-1949 (Box 44, Folder 349)
  - Rowntree Family - Rowntree, Peter (and Bessie) - Letters to, 1940-1949 (Box 44, Folder 350)
  - Rowntree Family - Rowntree, Peter (and Bessie) - Letters to, 1940-1949 (Box 44, Folder 351)
  - Rowntree Family - Rowntree, Peter (and Bessie) - Letters from, to sons Benjamin and David, 1942-1943 (Box 44, Folder 352)
  - Rowntree Family - Rowntree, Peter (and Bessie) - Evacuation and Return of Sons, 1940-1944 (Box 44, Folder 353)
  - Rowntree Family - Rowntree, Benjamin, 1944-1974, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 354)
  - Rowntree Family - Rowntree, Benjamin - Schooling, 1940-1942 (Box 44, Folder 355)
  - Rowntree Family - Rowntree, David, 1944-1961 (Box 44, Folder 356)
  - Rowntree Family - Rowntree, David - Schooling, 1940-1944 (Box 44, Folder 357)
  - Russia, 1987-1991 (Box 45, Folder 358)
  - Schools - Brearley School, 1946-1987 (Box 45, Folder 359)
  - Schools - Chapin School, 1973-1994 (Box 45, Folder 360)
  - Schools - Chapin School, 1973-1994 (Box 45, Folder 361)
  - Schools - Columbia University - Graduate Studies, 1954-1956 (Box 45, Folder 362)
  - Schools - Columbia University - Graduate Studies, 1954-1956 (Box 45, Folder 363)
  - Schools - Vassar College - Class Notes - Economics/French/Music (Box 46, Folder 364)
  - Schools - Vassar College - Class Notes - German/Music/Philosophy/History (Box 46, Folder 365)
  - Schools - Vassar College - Class Notes - Music History (Box 46, Folder 366)
  - Schools - Vassar College - Class Notes - Philosophy/Economics (Box 46, Folder 367)
  - Schools - Vassar College - Exams and Papers (Box 46, Folder 368)
  - Schools - Vassar College - Miscellany, 1928-1931 (Box 46, Folder 369)
  - Schools - Vassar College - General, 1962-1992 (Box 47, Folder 370)
  - Schools - Vassar College - General, 1962-1992 (Box 47, Folder 371)
  - Schools - Vassar College - Class of 1931, 1956-1992 (Box 47, Folder 372)
  - Schools - Vassar College - Contributions, 1963-1992 (Box 47, Folder 373)
  - Schools - Vassar College - Ferry Endowment Chair/Scholarships, 1966, 1976-1992 (Box 47, Folder 374)
  - Schools - Vassar College - Frances Lehman Loeb Art Center, 1986-1992 (Box 47, Folder 375)
  - Schools - Vassar College - Friends of the Vassar Art Gallery, 1980-1992 (Box 47, Folder 376)
  - Schools - Vassar College - Printed Material (Box 48, Folder 376A)
  - Speeches, 1934, 1971-1985 (Box 49, Folder 377)
  - Thailand, 1967-1991 (Box 49, Folder 378)
  - Travel - General Information and Documents (Box 49, Folder 379)
  - Travel - General Information and Documents (Box 49, Folder 380)
  - Travel - Memorabilia - Japan (Box 49, Folder 381)
  - Travel - Miscellany, 1933-1948 (Box 49, Folder 382)
  - Travel - Summer House - Marion, Massachusetts, 1939 (Box 49, Folder 383)
  - Travel - Trips, 1978-1985 (Box 49, Folder 384)
  - Travel - Trips, 1978-1985 (Box 49, Folder 385)
  - Travel - Trips, 1986-1992 (Box 50, Folder 386)
  - Travel - Trips, 1986-1992 (Box 50, Folder 387)
  - Travel - Trips, 1986-1992 (Box 50, Folder 388)
  - United China Relief, 1941-1942 (Box 50, Folder 389)
  - Vital Documents, 1909-1992 (Box 50, Folder 390)
  - Washington, D.C. Address Book, 1943 (Box 50, Folder 391)
  - Wedding - Ceremony, 1932 (Box 50, Folder 392)
  - Wedding - Invitations, 1932 (Box 50, Folder 393)
  - Wedding - Letters to Blanchette Hooker Rockefeller, 1932 (Box 50, Folder 394)
  - Wedding - Letters to Mrs. Elon H. Hooker, 1932 (Box 50, Folder 395)
  - Wedding - Lists - Index Cards, 1932 (Box 51, Folder 395A)
  - Wedding - Lists - Announcements, 1932 (Box 52, Folder 396)
  - Wedding - Lists - Ceremony Attendees, 1932 (Box 52, Folder 397)
  - Wedding - Lists - Gifts, 1932 (Box 52, Folder 398)
  - Wedding - Lists - Invitation, 1932 (Box 52, Folder 399)
  - Wedding - Lists - Reception, 1932 (Box 52, Folder 400)
  - Wedding - Lists - Reception, 1932 (Box 52, Folder 401)
  - Wedding - Lists - Scrapbook, 1932 (Box 52, Folder 402)
  - White House - Invitations, 1980-1989 (Box 52, Folder 403)